{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Sandblasting Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40009/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40009,"taskName":"Exterior Surfaces - Sandblasting","taskDescription":"Sandblast Surfaces","xmTaskDescriptor":"Sandblasting Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":304,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Exterior surfaces sandblast sand blast","textMessagingName":"Sandblast","rolloverLongDesc":"Very abrasive process usually limited to stripping paint or other coatings from masonry surfaces.  Sometimes used to prepare concrete for another layer.","rolloverShortDesc":"Compressed air throws sand to strip or clean.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Sandblast Surfaces.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Residential Sandblasting \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Sandblast an Exterior Surface","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":66,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Sandblast Exterior Surface","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Exterior Surfaces - Sandblasting","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Sandblasting Project","urlName":"Exterior-Surfaces-Sandblasting","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Residential Sandblasting Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Exterior,surfaces,sandblast,sand,blast,deck,paint,strip,concrete,clean,bead,surface,preperation,grit,shot,peening","emcCategoryOid":-12062,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":333,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40009/":{"taskOID":40009,"originalTaskOID":40009,"setID":333,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5419,"questionDisplayText":"Material to be Sandblasted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the area or item(s) that need to be sandblasted. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2806,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Glass","answerDisplayText":"Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1270,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Area Needing Sandblasting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the area or item to be sandblasted?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Removal of exterior paint","answerDisplayText":"Removal of exterior paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1416,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Clean old or tarnished object","answerDisplayText":"Clean old or tarnished object","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6096,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stone etching","answerDisplayText":"Stone etching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2810,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Glass etching","answerDisplayText":"Glass etching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6358,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tile etching","answerDisplayText":"Tile etching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6928,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Weather wood","answerDisplayText":"Weather wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5419,"questionDisplayText":"Material to be Sandblasted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the area or item(s) that need to be sandblasted. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2806,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Glass","answerDisplayText":"Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3803,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Metal","answerDisplayText":"Metal","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1553,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2806,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Glass","answerDisplayText":"Glass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1270,"questionDisplayText":"Description of Area Needing Sandblasting","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the area or item to be sandblasted?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Removal of exterior paint","answerDisplayText":"Removal of exterior paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1416,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Clean old or tarnished object","answerDisplayText":"Clean old or tarnished object","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6096,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stone etching","answerDisplayText":"Stone etching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2810,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Glass etching","answerDisplayText":"Glass etching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6358,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tile etching","answerDisplayText":"Tile etching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6928,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Weather wood","answerDisplayText":"Weather wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5159,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Removal of exterior paint","answerDisplayText":"Removal of exterior paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1416,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Clean old or tarnished object","answerDisplayText":"Clean old or tarnished object","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6096,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stone etching","answerDisplayText":"Stone etching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2810,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Glass etching","answerDisplayText":"Glass etching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6358,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tile etching","answerDisplayText":"Tile etching","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6928,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Weather wood","answerDisplayText":"Weather wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}